Guide to the Gerald H. Anderson Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Writings, Lectures, Research Files, 1957-2012; Series II
  - Regarding booklength works
    - Biographical Dictionary of Christian Mission
      - Articles File
        - Stewart, James (Box 24, Folder 2569)
        - Stewart, John (Box 24, Folder 2570)
        - Stirling, Waite Hocking (Box 24, Folder 2571)
        - Stock, Eugene (Box 24, Folder 2572)
        - Stockfleth, Nils Joachim (Box 24, Folder 2573)
        - Stockton, Betsy (Box 24, Folder 2574)
        - Stockwell, B(owman) Foster (Box 24, Folder 2575)
        - Stockwell, Eugene L(ouden) (Box 24, Folder 2576)
        - Stone, Mary (Shi Meiyu) (Box 24, Folder 2577)
        - Stosch, Johannes Richard Andreas (Box 24, Folder 2578)
        - Stott, John R. W. (Box 24, Folder 2579)
        - Stover, Wilbur B. (Box 24, Folder 2580)
        - Strachan, Harry (Box 24, Folder 2581)
        - Strachan, R. Kenneth (Box 24, Folder 2582)
        - Strachan, Susan Beamish (Box 24, Folder 2583)
        - Strauss, Hermann (Box 24, Folder 2584)
        - Strehlow, Carl Friedrich T. (Box 24, Folder 2585)
        - Streicher, Henri (Box 24, Folder 2586)
        - Streit, Karl (Box 24, Folder 2587)
        - Streit, Robert (Box 24, Folder 2588)
        - Stronach, Alexander (Box 24, Folder 2589)
        - Stronach, John (Box 24, Folder 2590)
        - Strong, Josiah (Box 24, Folder 2591)
        - Struve, Nikita (Box 24, Folder 2592)
        - Stuart, Edward Craig (Box 24, Folder 2593)
        - Stuart, John Leighton (Box 24, Folder 2594)
        - Studd, Charles Thomas (Box 24, Folder 2595)
        - Studd, J. E. K. (Box 24, Folder 2596)
        - Sturges, Albert A. (Box 24, Folder 2597)
        - Sturmius (Box 24, Folder 2598)
        - Stursberg, (Englebert) (Box 24, Folder 2599)
        - Subban, John (Box 24, Folder 2600)
        - Suchanov, Cyril (Box 24, Folder 2601)
        - Suidbert (also Suitbert or Swibert) (Box 24, Folder 2602)
        - Singh, Sunder (Box 24, Folder 2603)
        - Suh, San-Yuh (Box 24, Folder 2604)
        - Sundkler, Bengt (Box 24, Folder 2605)
        - Sung, John Shang-Chieh (Box 24, Folder 2606)
        - Sutton, Amos (Box 24, Folder 2607)
        - Swain, Clara A. (Box 24, Folder 2608)
        - Swainson, Florence (Box 24, Folder 2609)
        - Swan, William (Box 24, Folder 2610)
        - Swatson, John (Box 24, Folder 2611)
        - Sweetman, James Windrow (Box 24, Folder 2612)
        - Szabo, Aladar (Box 24, Folder 2613)
        - Takayaama, Justus Ukon (Box 24, Folder 2614)
        - Takl, John (Box 24, Folder 2615)
        - Takla Haymenot (Box 24, Folder 2616)
        - Talmage, John Van Nest (Box 24, Folder 2617)
        - Tarkkanen, M. (Box 24, Folder 2618)
        - Tambunan, A. M. (Box 24, Folder 2619)
        - Tatlow, Tissington (Box 24, Folder 2620)
        - Ta'unga (Box 24, Folder 2621)
        - Taylor, James Hudson (Box 24, Folder 2622)
        - Taylor, Clyde W. (Box 24, Folder 2623)
        - Taylor, John Christopher (Box 24, Folder 2624)
        - Taylor, John V(ernon) (Box 24, Folder 2625)
        - Taylor, Maria Dyer (Box 24, Folder 2626)
        - Taylor, Richard (Box 24, Folder 2627)
        - Taylor, Richard W. (Box 24, Folder 2628)
        - Taylor, william (Box 24, Folder 2629)
        - Teague, Colin (Box 24, Folder 2630)
        - Teava (Box 24, Folder 2631)
        - Tellstrom, Carl (Box 24, Folder 2632)
        - Tempels, Placide (Francois) (Box 24, Folder 2633)
        - Temple, Wiliam (Box 25, Folder 2634)
        - Teresa of Lisieux (Box 25, Folder 2635)
        - Teresa, Mother (Agnes Gonxha Bojaxhiv) (Box 25, Folder 2636)
        - Testera, Jacob de (Box 25, Folder 2637)
        - Tewksbury, E.G. (Box 25, Folder 2638)
        - Thauren, Johannes (Box 25, Folder 2639)
        - Theile, Otto (Box 25, Folder 2640)
        - Thevenoud, Johanny (Box 25, Folder 2641)
        - Thoburn, Isabella (Box 25, Folder 2642)
        - Thoburn, James Mills (Box 25, Folder 2643)
        - Thomas, John (Box 25, Folder 2644)
        - Thomas, John 1757-1801 (Box 25, Folder 2645)
        - Thomas, John 1796-1881 (Box 25, Folder 2646)
        - Thomas, Mary Davies (Box 25, Folder 2647)
        - Thomas M(adathiparampil) M(ammen) (Box 25, Folder 2648)
        - Thomas, Robert Jermain (Box 25, Folder 2649)
        - Th0mas of Jesus (Box 25, Folder 2650)
        - Thomson James (Diego) (Box 25, Folder 2651)
        - Thomson, John Fancis (Box 25, Folder 2652)
        - Thomson, William Ritchie (Box 25, Folder 2653)
        - Thompson, Thomas (Box 25, Folder 2654)
        - Thompson, Ralph Wardlaw (Box 25, Folder 26 55)
        - Thornton, Douglas M. L. (Box 25, Folder 2656)
        - Threlkeld, Lancelot Edward (Box 25, Folder 2657)
        - Thurston, Asa and Lucy (Box 25, Folder 2658)
        - Thurston (Mrs Lawrence) Matilda S. Calder (Box 25, Folder 2659)
        - Tikhomirov, Sergie (Box 25, Folder 2660)
        - Tilak, Narayan Vaman (Box 25, Folder 2661)
        - Tile, Nehemiah (Box 25, Folder 2662)
        - Timpan, Americus Vespucci (Box 25, Folder 2663)
        - Ting, K. H. (Box 25, Folder 2664)
        - Ting, Li-Mei (Box 25, Folder 2665)
        - Tippett, Alan R. (Box 25, Folder 2666)
        - Titus, Murray Thurston (Box 25, Folder 2667)
        - Tisdell, william St Clair (Box 25, Folder 2668)
        - Todd, Garfield (Box 25, Folder 2669)
        - Tollefsen, Gunnerius Olai (Box 25, Folder 2670)
        - Tomlin, Jacob (Box 25, Folder 2671)
        - Toribio, Alonso de Mogrovejo, Alfonso (Box 25, Folder 2671a)
        - Torrance, David Watt (Box 25, Folder 2672)
        - Torrance, Thomas (Box 25, Folder 2673)
        - Torrend, Jules (Box 25, Folder 2674)
        - Tosari, Paulus (Box 25, Folder 2675)
        - Toth, Alexis (Box 25, Folder 2676)
        - Tournon, Charles Thomas (Box 25, Folder 2677)
        - Townsend, Henry (Box 25, Folder 2678)
        - Townsend, Henry (Box 25, Folder 2679)
        - Townsend, William Cameron (Box 25, Folder 2680)
        - Trasher, Lillian Hunt (Box 25, Folder 2681)
        - Tragella, Giovanni Battista (Box 25, Folder 2682)
        - Trenchard, Ernest (Box 25, Folder 2683)
        - Trigault, Nicolas (Box 25, Folder 2684)
        - Trobe, Christian la Ignatius (Box 25, Folder 2685)
        - Trobish, Walter and Ingrid Hult (Box 25, Folder 2686)
        - Troeltsch, Ernst (Box 25, Folder 2687)
        - Trollope, Mark Napier (Box 25, Folder 2688)
        - Trotman, Dwson (Box 25, Folder 2689)
        - Trotter, Isabelle (Box 25, Folder 2690)
        - Trudpert (Box 25, Folder 2691)
        - Trumbull, David (Box 25, Folder 2692)
        - Trumpp, Ernst (Box 25, Folder 2693)
        - Truxton, James C. (Box 25, Folder 2694)
        - Tryphon of Pechenga (Box 25, Folder 2695)
        - Tsizehena, John (Box 25, Folder 2696)
        - Tucker, Alfred Robert (Box 25, Folder 2697)
        - Tucker, Charlotet (Box 25, Folder 2698)
        - Tucker, Henry Carre (Box 25, Folder 2699)
        - Tucker, John Taylor (Box 25, Folder 2700)
        - Tucker, J. W. (Box 25, Folder 27001)
        - Tucker, John Thomas (Box 25, Folder 2702)
        - Tule, Mary Branton (Box 25, Folder 2703)
        - Tunggul Wulung, Kjai Ibrahim (Box 25, Folder 2704)
        - Tupou (Taafa'ahau) George (Box 25, Folder 2705)
        - Turner, George (Box 25, Folder 2706)
        - Turner, Harold W. (Box 25, Folder 2707)
        - Turner, Henry McNeal (Box 25, Folder 2708)
        - Turquetil, Arsane (Box 25, Folder 2709)
        - Turton, William (Box 25, Folder 2710)
        - Tyler, Josiah (Box 25, Folder 2711)
        - Tyndale-Biscoe, Cecil E. (Box 25, Folder 2712)
        - Uchimura, Kanzo (Box 25, Folder 2713)
        - Uemura, Masahisa (Box 25, Folder 2714)
        - Ulfilas (Box 25, Folder 2715)
        - Underhill, Edward Bean (Box 25, Folder 2716)
        - Underwood, Horace Grant and Lillias (Box 25, Folder 2717)
        - Upadhaya Brahmabandhav (Box 25, Folder 2718)
        - Urban VIII (Maffeo Barberini) (Box 25, Folder 2719)
        - Urdaneta, Andres de (Box 25, Folder 2720)
        - Urios, Saturnino (Box 25, Folder 2721)
        - Urlsperger, Johann August (Box 25, Folder 2722)
        - Vahl, Jens (Box 25, Folder 2723)
        - Valdes, Diego (Box 25, Folder 2724)
        - Valdivia, Luis de (Box 25, Folder 2725)
        - Valencia, Martin de (Box 25, Folder 2726)
        - Valdivieso, Antonio de (Box 25, Folder 2727)
        - Valentinus (Box 25, Folder 2728)
        - Valignano, Alessandro (Box 25, Folder 2729)
        - Valle, Juan del (Box 25, Folder 2730)
        - Van Andel, H. A. (Box 25, Folder 2731)
        - Van, Bulck, Gaasto (Vaast) (Box 25, Folder 2732)
        - Van der Kamp, Johannes Theodorus (Box 25, Folder 733)
        - Van de Loosdrecht, A. A. (Box 25, Folder 2734)
        - Van Dyck, C. V. A. (Box 25, Folder 2735)
        - Van Leeuwen, Arend Th. (Box 25, Folder 2735a)
        - Van Sambeek, Jan Martin Cornelius (Box 25, Folder 2736)
        - Van Wing, Joseph (Box 26, Folder 2737)
        - Vasco, de Quiroga (Box 26, Folder 2738)
        - Vasconcelos, Simaeo de (Box 26, Folder 2739)
        - Vath, Alfons (Box 26, Folder 2740)
        - Vaughan,Herbert Alfred (Box 26, Folder 2741)
        - Vautrin, Wilhelmina (Box 26, Folder 2742)
        - Vaz, Joseph (Box 26, Folder 2743)
        - Vedder, Heinrich (Box 26, Folder 2744)
        - Veenstra, Johanna (Box 26, Folder 2745)
        - Venard, Jean Theophane (Box 26, Folder 2746)
        - Venn, Henry (Box 26, Folder 2747)
        - Venn, John (Box 26, Folder 2748)
        - Vennard, Iva May Durham (Box 26, Folder 2749)
        - Vera Cruz, Alonso de la (Box 26, Folder 2750)
        - Verbeck, Guido Fridolin (Box 26, Folder 2751)
        - Verbist, Theophile (Box 26, Folder 2752)
        - Verbiest, Ferdinand (Box 26, Folder 2753)
        - Verius (Verjus), Stanislao Enrico (Box 26, Folder 2754)
        - Verkuyl, Johannes (Box 26, Folder 2755)
        - Vernier, Jean-Frederic (Box 26, Folder 2756)
        - Veronis, Alexander (Box 26, Folder 2757)
        - Vialar, Emilie de (Box 26, Folder 2758)
        - Vicedom, Georg Friedrich (Box 26, Folder 2759)
        - Vicelin (Box 26, Folder 2760)
        - Victor, Janos (Box 26, Folder 2761)
        - Vidal, Owen Emeric (Box 26, Folder 2762)
        - Vieira, Antonio de (Box 26, Folder 2763)
        - Vieter, Heinrich (Box 26, Folder 2764)
        - Vietor, J. (Box 26, Folder 2765)
        - Villaverde, Juan (Box 26, Folder 2766)
        - Vingren, Adolf Gunnar (Box 26, Folder 2767)
        - Villota Y Urroz, Gerardo (Box 26, Folder 2768)
        - Vining, Leslie Gordon (Box 26, Folder 2769)
        - Vinco, Angelo (Box 26, Folder 2770)
        - Vincent de Paul (Box 26, Folder 2771)
        - Vinton, Justus Hatch and Calista H. (Box 26, Folder 2772)
        - Virgil of Salzburg (Box 26, Folder 2773)
        - Visdelou, Claude de (Box 26, Folder 2774)
        - Visser 't Hooft, Willem Adolf (Box 26, Folder 2775)
        - Vitoria, Francisco de (Box 26, Folder 2776)
        - Vives, Juan Bautista (Box 26, Folder 2777)
        - Vladimir of Kiev (Box 26, Folder 2778)
        - Voetius, Gisbertus (Box 26, Folder 2779)
        - Von Westen, Thomas (Box 26, Folder 2780)
        - Von Zaremba, Felican (Box 26, Folder 2781)
        - Vories, William Merrell (Box 26, Folder 2782)
        - Voronaev, Ivan (Box 26, Folder 2783)
        - Vos, Michael Christian (Box 26, Folder 2784)
        - Voscamp, Carl J. (Box 26, Folder 2785)
        - Voth, Henry B. (Box 26, Folder 2786)
        - Waddell, Hope Masterton (Box 26, Folder 2787)
        - Wade, Jonathan and Deborah (Box 26, Folder 2788)
        - Wagenseil, Johann Christoph (Box 26, Folder 2789)
        - Wakefield, Thomas (Box 26, Folder 2790)
        - Walaeus, Antonius (Box 26, Folder 2791)
        - Waldo (Valdez), Peter (Box 26, Folder 2792)
        - Walker, Thomas (Box 26, Folder 2793)
        - Walker, William (Box 26, Folder 2794)
        - Waller, Edward Harry (Box 26, Folder 2795)
        - Walls, Andrew Finlay (Box 26, Folder 2796)
        - Walpot, Peter (Box 26, Folder 2797)
        - Walsh, James Anthony (Box 26, Folder 2798)
        - Walsh, James E. (Box 26, Folder 2799)
        - Walther, Christof (Box 26, Folder 2800)
        - Wang, Mingdao (Box 26, Folder 2801)
        - Wangemann, Hermann Theodore (Box 26, Folder 2802)
        - Wangerin, Theodora S. (Box 26, Folder 2803)
        - Wanless, William (Box 26, Folder 2804)
        - Wanyoike, Wa Kamawe (Box 26, Folder 2805)
        - Ward, William (Box 26, Folder 2806)
        - Wardlaw, John Smith (Box 26, Folder 2807)
        - Warnshuis, Abbe Livingston (Box 26, Folder 2808)
        - Warneck, Gustav (Box 26, Folder 2809)
        - Warneck, Johnnes (Box 26, Folder 2810)
        - Warren, Max A. C. (Box 26, Folder 2812)
        - Watson, Minnie (Box 26, Folder 2813)
        - Watson, William (Box 26, Folder 2814)
        - Way, Lewis (Box 26, Folder 2815)
        - Webb, Mary (Box 26, Folder 2816)
        - Webster, James (Box 26, Folder 2817)
        - Webster-Smith, Irene (Box 26, Folder 2818)
        - Weerasooriya, Arnolis (Box 26, Folder 2819)
        - Wei, Francis C(ho) M(in) (Box 26, Folder 2820)
        - Weinland, William (Box 26, Folder 2821)
        - Weir, Andrew (Box 26, Folder 2822)
        - Welch, James E. (Box 26, Folder 2823)
        - Welz, Justinian Von (Box 26, Folder 2824)
        - Wenger, John (Box 26, Folder 2825)
        - Wesley, Charles (Box 26, Folder 2826)
        - Wesley, John (Box 26, Folder 2827)
        - Westcott, Brooke Foss (Box 26, Folder 2828)
        - Westcott, Foss (Box 26, Folder 2829)
        - Westermann, Diedrich Hermann (Box 26, Folder 2830)
        - Westman, Knut B (Box 26, Folder 2831)
        - Weston, Frank (Box 26, Folder 2832)
        - Westropp, Clara (Box 26, Folder 2833)
        - Wheelock, Eleazer (Box 26, Folder 2834)
        - Wherry, Elwood moris (Box 26, Folder 2835)
        - White, Andrew (Box 26, Folder 2836)
        - White, Charlotte (Box 26, Folder 2837)
        - White, Elen Gould (Harmon) (Box 26, Folder 2838)
        - Whitefield, George (Box 26, Folder 2839)
        - White, Frank Hall (Box 26, Folder 2840)
        - White, Hugh Vernon (Box 26, Folder 2841)
        - White, John (Box 26, Folder 2842)
        - White, John Campbell (Box 26, Folder 2843)
        - White, M. C. (Box 26, Folder 2844)
        - White, Paul (Box 26, Folder 2845)
        - Whiting, J. B. (Box 26, Folder 2846)
        - Whitehead, Henry (Box 26, Folder 2847)
        - Whitman, Marcus and Narcissa Prentiss (Box 26, Folder 2848)
        - Whittemore, Emma (Box 26, Folder 2849)
        - Wicki, Jos. (Box 26, Folder 2850)
        - Widmann, Rosina (Box 26, Folder 2851)
        - Wilberforce, Samuel (Box 27, Folder 2852)
        - Wilberforce, William (Box 27, Folder 2853)
        - Wilder, Grace (Box 27, Folder 2854)
        - Wilder, Robert Parmelee (Box 27, Folder 2855)
        - Wilder, Royal Gould (Box 27, Folder 2856)
        - Wieger, George Frederic Leon (Box 27, Folder 2857)
        - Wilfrid (Box 27, Folder 2858)
        - Wilkes, A. Paget (Box 27, Folder 2859)
        - Wilkins, Ann (Box 27, Folder 2860)
        - Willehad (Box 27, Folder 2861)
        - Willeke, Bernward H. (Box 27, Folder 2862)
        - William of Tripoli (Box 27, Folder 2863)
        - William of Rusbruck (also Ruysbroekor Ruysbrock) (Box 27, Folder 2864)
        - Williams, Channing Moore (Box 27, Folder 2865)
        - Williams, Henry (Box 27, Folder 2866)
        - Williams, John E. (Box 27, Folder 2867)
        - Williams, John and Mary (Box 27, Folder 2868)
        - Williams, Ralph Darby (Box 27, Folder 2869)
        - Williams, Roger (Box 27, Folder 2870)
        - Williams, Samuel Wells (Box 27, Folder 2871)
        - Williams, William (Box 27, Folder 2872)
        - Williams, William Frederic (Box 27, Folder 2873)
        - Williamson, Alexander (Box 27, Folder 2874)
        - Williamson, Henry Raymond (Box 27, Folder 2875)
        - Williamson, Thomas S. (Box 27, Folder 2876)
        - Willibald (Box 27, Folder 2877)
        - Willibrord (Box 27, Folder 2878)
        - Willis, J. J. (Box 27, Folder 2879)
        - Willoughby, W. C (Box 27, Folder 2880)
        - Wilson, C.E (Box 27, Folder 2881)
        - Wilson, Daniel (Box 27, Folder 2882)
        - Wilson, Edward Francis (Box 27, Folder 2883)
        - Wilson, Eleanor (Box 27, Folder 2884)
        - Wilson, James (Box 27, Folder 2885)
        - Wilson, John Leighton (Box 27, Folder 2886)
        - Wilson, J. christy Sr. (Box 27, Folder 2887)
        - Wilson, John and Margaret (Box 27, Folder 2888)
        - Wilson, Mary Ann Cooke (Box 27, Folder 2889)
        - Wilson, Robert O. (Box 27, Folder 2890)
        - Wilson, Samuel Graham (Box 27, Folder 2891)
        - Wimmer, Gottlieb August (Box 27, Folder 2892)
        - Winans, Roger and Ester (Box 27, Folder 2893)
        - Winslow, John ("Jack") Copley (Box 27, Folder 2894)
        - Winslow, Harriet Lathrop (Box 27, Folder 2895)
        - Winslow, Miron (Box 27, Folder 2896)
        - Winter, Ralph D(ana) (Box 27, Folder 2897)
        - Winthuis, Josef (Box 27, Folder 2898)
        - Wiser, William and Charlotte (Box 27, Folder 2899)
        - Witte, Johannes (Box 27, Folder 2900)
        - Wolfgang (Box 27, Folder 2901)
        - Wolff, Joseph (Box 27, Folder 2902)
        - Wood, A. H. (Box 27, Folder 2903)
        - Wood, Thomas Bond (Box 27, Folder 2904)
        - Woods, Charles Stacey (Box 27, Folder 2905)
        - Woolston, Sarah and Beulah (Box 27, Folder 2906)
        - Worcester, Samuel AustinWright, Frank Hall (Box 27, Folder 2907)
        - Wright, Frank Hall (Box 27, Folder 2908)
        - Wu, Li (Box 27, Folder 2909)
        - Wu, Y. T. (Box 27, Folder 2910)
        - Wurz, Friedrich (Box 27, Folder 2911)
        - Wylie, Alexander (Box 27, Folder 2912)
        - Xavier, Francis (Francisco de Jassu Y Xavier) (Box 27, Folder 2913)
        - Xavier, Jerome (Box 27, Folder 2914)
        - Xenos of Crete (Box 27, Folder 2915)
        - Xu, Candida (Box 27, Folder 2916)
        - Yamamuro, Gumpei (Box 27, Folder 2917)
        - Yang, T'ing-yun (Box 27, Folder 2918)
        - Yannoulatos, Anastasios (Box 27, Folder 2919)
        - Yate, William (Box 27, Folder 2920)
        - Yates, Matthew Tyson (Box 27, Folder 2921)
        - Yates, William (Box 27, Folder 2922)
        - Yen, James Y. C. (Box 27, Folder 2923)
        - Yergan, Max (Box 27, Folder 2924)
        - Yi, Keui-Poong (Box 27, Folder 2925)
        - Ying, Lianzhi (Box 27, Folder 2926)
        - Yoder, Charles Frances (Box 27, Folder 2927)
        - Young, Florence (Box 27, Folder 2928)
        - Young, George Armstrong (Box 27, Folder 2929)
        - Young, S. Hall (Box 27, Folder 2930)
        - Young, T(hmas) Cullen (Box 27, Folder 2931)
        - Yu Kuo-Chen (Box 27, Folder 2932)
        - Yun, Tchi-Ho (Box 27, Folder 2933)
        - Yui, David Z. T. (Box 27, Folder 2934)
        - Zahn, Franz Micheal (Box 27, Folder 2935)
        - Zakaryas (Box 27, Folder 2936)
        - Zaleski, Vladislaus Michael (Box 27, Folder 2937)
        - Zameza, Jose (Box 27, Folder 2938)
        - Zaplata, Feliks (Box 27, Folder 2939)
        - Zeiberger, David (Box 27, Folder 2940)
        - Zeng, Boasun (Box 27, Folder 2941)
        - Ziegenbalg, Bartholomeus (Box 27, Folder 2942)
        - Zimmermann, Johannes and Catherine (Box 27, Folder 2943)
        - Zinzendorf, Nicholaus Ludwig Von (Box 27, Folder 2944)
        - Zumarrga (Cumarraga) Juan de (Box 27, Folder 2945)
        - Zwemer, Samuel Marinus (Box 27, Folder 2946)
        - Zwingli, Ulrich (or Huldriech) (Box 27, Folder 2947)
      - Correspondence and Financial Records
        - Payment to authors
          - A-Z (Box 28, Folder 2948-2971)
          - Correspondence in connection with Payment Record, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 2972)
        - Instructions to Contributors and Editors
          - Instructions, 1993-1996, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 2973-2979)
        - General Correspondence with Publishers
          - Correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 28, Folder 2980-2986)
          - Correspondence with Publishers concerning World Map, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 2987)
      - Addendum 2012
        - Correspondence with publisher, 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence with authors and consultants, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence with authors and consultants, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Witness to World Christianity: The International Association for Mission Studies, 1972-2012 (2012)
      - Correspondence
        - Bonk, Jonathan, 2005-2012 (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - Camps, Arnulf; Conway, Martin, 2003-2008 (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - Grundmann, Christoffer, 2008-2011 (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - H - K, incl. Willi Henkel, Anne-Marie Kool, Jan Jongeneel, 2007-2010 (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - Myklebust, Olav, 1971-1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - Nygaard, Birger, 2004-2011 (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - Prior, John / BISAM, 2010-2011 (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Ross, Cathy, 2009-2011 (Box 33, Folder 11)
        - Roxborogh, John, 2005-2010 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Roxborogh, John, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - R - S, incl. Karl Schaefer, Wilbert Shenk (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Verstraelen, Frans, 2005-2009 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Walls, Andrew, 2007-2010 (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - V - W, incl. Jan van Butselaar, Darrell Whiteman, Joachim Wietzke (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Notes and documents
        - General (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - DABOH, 1973-2008 (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - History of missiology in America, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 9)
        - Olav Myklebust writings, 1986, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 10)
        - Selly Oak Consultation, 1968, 1968-2008 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Lectures and addresses
    - Lectures on future of missions given at conferences, including Episcopal Clergy Conference, 1976-1980 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Address to Presbyterian Church in the U.S. Division of International Mission planning conference, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Belk Lectures, Wesleyan College, Macon, GA (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Orlando E. Costas Memorial Service, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Yale Divinity School sermon, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - E. Stanley Jones Lecture, Boston University School of Theology, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Asbury Theological Seminary, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Remarks at banquet for Arthur Glasser, Fuller Theological Seminary, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Yale Divinity School sermon, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Remarks at luncheon following installation of Charles Van Engen, Fuller Seminary, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Tribute to Lesslie Newbigin at Samford University, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Response to paper by Paul Pierson at Ethics and Public Policy Center, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Lecture at IIMO, Utrecht, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Lecture at Gurukul Theological Collee, Chennai, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Scherer Lecture, Chicago Center for Global Ministries, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Remarks at Union Theological Seminary, Manila, unidentified talk, 2008, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Reports and other writings
    - Book reviews, book notes, 1960-1968 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Overseas Ministries Study Center Director reports, 1994-2000 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Overseas Ministries Study Center reports on study leaves, to Personnel Committee, 1985-1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Other reports, 2005, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Research files
    - Christianity in the Philippines, 1957-1963 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Christianity in the Philippines, 1949-1963 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Christianity in the Philippines, 1955-1961 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Christianity in the Philippines, 1961-1994 (Box 36, Folder 1)